# **VIDHYA RAJENDRAN**

Senior Associate with 12 + Years of experience in Business banking operations. To be a professional of an esteemed organization that gives me scope to update my knowledge and technical skills in accordance with the latest trends and be an associate of a team that dynamically workd towards growth of organization and gains satisfaction. Strengths include the ability to adapt quickly to new environment and new type of projects.

⋈ kuttisuji22@gmail.com

9790777055

Chennai.India

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Senior Associate**

Mashreq Global Services Pvt Ltd. - Bangalore, India.

May 2021 - Present

Onboarding merchant Services

Best Performer Award

#### **Process Advisor**

Barclays Shared Services Pvt Ltd.,

Nov 2010 - Jan 2014 & Mar 2015 - Sep 2019

• Won Super Star Award / Champion of the day / Hi-flyer Award twice

#### **Senior Customer Service Executive**

Intelenet Global Services Pvt Ltd.

Nov 2006 - Apr 2010

Won Spot Awards

# **EDUCATION**

- · Bachelor of commerce in Madras University (2002-2005)
- Diploma in Executive Secretary ship from Stenographers Guild
- Higher both in shorthand & typewriting (First Class)

# **SKILLS**

Customer Due Diligence Preparing MIS reports Maintenance **Quality Check New Hire Training** 

# **LANGUAGES**

English Tamil

# **Roles and Responsibilities**

- Verifying KYC Documents for all merchants on boarded.
- Verification of data input on system for setup and maintenance of merchants, creating TID's and MID's activation.
- Handling of merchant queries, pro-active resolution of issues in timely manner.
- Processing setup of merchants accurately as per the details on merchant setup forms.
- Processing maintenance of merchants as per requests from merchants and RM's
- Complete understanding of merchant setups and payments to handle all types of queries received from merchants and appropriate tracking.
- Worked applications like Prime, Sail, Flex and other bank applications and research tools.
- Worked as a team to complete the SLA.
- Performing identification & Verification checks through Mastercard connect, Website check, Flex,
  World check on all on-boarding clients to identify and sail hit.
- Undertaken, Quality Check on daily basis to maintain good quality to achieve the Team performance errors.
- Handling queue efficiently
- Liaise with RM's and sales co-ordinators on a daily basis regarding escalations and queries